<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Foods on my trip navigation</title>
    <link>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Foods on my trip navigation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 03:48:47 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://usehttps.github.io/foods/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Spain</title>
      <link>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/spain/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 03:48:47 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/spain/</guid>
      <description>Foods you must try Famous foods top 5 Gazpacho Paella (seafood paella) Tortilla Española (Spanish omelet) Gambas al ajillo (garlic soup) Tostas de tomate y jamón Famous Sweets Churros con Chocolate (Spanish Churros with Chocolate) Polvorón is simple shortbread which is made out of flour, sugar and milk. Famous Drinks Sangria Horchata is an iced rice milk beverage from Mexico that’s a simple blend of rice, cinnamon, milk and sweetener. It’s a sweet and creamy delight Famous Fruits Food trivia Está delicioso means &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s delicious&amp;rdquo; According to culinary historians, mayonnaise was first prepared by a French chef in 1756 as a part of a victory feast for capturing the Port Mahon located on the island of Minorca, Spain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Macau</title>
      <link>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/macau/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 10:43:23 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/macau/</guid>
      <description>Foods you must try Famous foods top 5 咖哩蟹 非洲雞 葡式焗鴨飯 猪扒包 煲仔飯 Famous Sweets 豆花 葡式蛋撻 木糠布甸 杏仁餅 鮮蚕巻 Famous Drinks Macau beer Famous Fruits Food trivia xxx means &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s delicious&amp;rdquo; Other famous foods 燒馬介休 咖哩牛雜・咖哩魚蛋 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ireland</title>
      <link>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/ireland/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 09:57:12 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/ireland/</guid>
      <description>Foods you must try Famous foods top 5 Irish Stew Irish Soda Bread Ulster Fry Colcannon Mash and Champ Shepherd&amp;rsquo;s Pie Famous Sweets Yellowman Sweet Famous Drinks Famous Fruits Food trivia xxx means &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s delicious&amp;rdquo; Other famous foods Irish White Pudding Bacon and Cabbage Irish Barmbrack Boxty Shellfish Coddle Potato Farls or Potato Bread </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand</title>
      <link>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/newzealand/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 10:45:26 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/newzealand/</guid>
      <description>Foods you must try Famous foods top 5 Crayfish and seafood New Zealand lamb Hāngī - food cooked under the ground Fish and chips Savoury Pies Famous Sweets New Zealand pavlova and fruit salad New Zealand lollies, chocolate and sweet treats Jaffas Manuka Honey Hokey Pokey Ice Cream Real Fruit Ice Cream Chocolate Fish Greenshell Mussels Famous Drinks L&amp;amp;P: stands for “Lemon &amp;amp; Paeroa” named after the North Island town it was invented in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Canada</title>
      <link>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/canada/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 02:26:25 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/canada/</guid>
      <description>Foods you must try Famous foods top 5 Lobster Poutine Beavertails Alberta Beef Sandwich Shepherd&amp;rsquo;s pie Famous Sweets Maple syrup Nanaimo bar S&amp;rsquo;more Apple Crumble Pie Butter Tart Famous Drinks Caesar: A Caesar is a cocktail created and consumed primarily in Canada. It typically contains vodka, tomato juice and clam broth, hot sauce, and Worcestershire sauce, and is served with ice in a large, celery salt-rimmed glass, typically garnished with a stalk of celery and wedge of lime.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uk</title>
      <link>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/uk/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 19:34:38 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/uk/</guid>
      <description>Foods you must try Famous food top 5 Fish and chips Cottage pie / Shepherd’s pie: Shepherd&amp;rsquo;s pie, cottage pie, or in its French version hachis Parmentier is a savoury dish of cooked minced meat topped with mashed potato and baked. The meat used may be either previously cooked or freshly minced. The usual meats are beef or lamb. Roast beef Haggis: Haggis is a savoury pudding containing sheep&amp;rsquo;s pluck, minced with onion, oatmeal, suet, spices, and salt, mixed with stock, and cooked while traditionally encased in the animal&amp;rsquo;s stomach though now an artificial casing is often used instead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japan</title>
      <link>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/japan/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 18:03:34 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/japan/</guid>
      <description>Foods you must try Famous food top 5 Sushi寿司: Ramenラーメン Onigiriおにぎり Miso Soup味噌汁 Udonうどん Famous Sweets Japanese Cheesecake Castella Cake Matcha Swiss Roll Dorayaki (Japanese Red Bean Pancake) Warabi Mochi Dango Nama Chocolate Purin (Japanese Custard Pudding) Matcha Tiramisu Japanese Strawberry Shortcake Fluffy Japanese Pancakes Taiyaki (Japanese Fish-Shaped Cake Waffle) Anmitsu Mochi Ice Cream Pon de Ring Donuts Daifuku Mochi Coffee Jelly Sakura Mochi Famous Drinks Sencha Chūhai Awamori Highball (Japan) Umeshu Shōchū Matcha Sake Amazake Pocari Sweat Caplico (Calpis) Japanese Whiskey Food trivia Oishii, Umai (美味しい、うまい) means &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s delicious&amp;rdquo; Other famous foods Tempura　天ぷら Karaage　唐揚げ Yakitori　焼き鳥 Sashimi　刺身 Donburi(Gyudon)　牛丼 Natto　納豆 Oden　おでん Tamagoyaki　卵焼き Soba　そば Tonkatsu　豚カツ Kashi Pan　菓子パン Sukiyaki　すき焼き Okonomiyaki　お好み焼き Mentaiko　明太子 Nikujaga　肉じゃが Curry Rice　カレーライス Unaju うな重 ShabuShabu Hot Pot　しゃぶしゃぶ鍋 Gyoza　餃子 Takoyaki　たこ焼き Edamame　枝豆 Chawanmushi　茶碗蒸し </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Australia</title>
      <link>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/australia/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 00:38:03 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/australia/</guid>
      <description>Foods you must try Famous food top 5 Vegemite: is a thick, dark brown Australian food spread made from leftover brewers&amp;rsquo; yeast extract with various vegetable and spice additives. Aussie Meat Pies: In Australia and New Zealand, a meat pie is a hand-sized pie containing diced or minced meat and gravy, sometimes with onion, mushrooms, or cheese. Chicken Parmigiana: Chicken parmigiana (pollo alla parmigiana in Italian!) is known in Australia as Parm, Parma, or Parmi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Usa</title>
      <link>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/usa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 10:42:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/usa/</guid>
      <description>Foods you must try Famous food top 5 Hamburger Pizza Hot dog Macaroni and cheese (Mac’n Cheese) Fried Chicken Famous Sweets Apple Pie Donuts Ice cream Oreo Chocolate chip Cookies(Soft Cookie、Chewy Cookie) S&amp;rsquo;mores Peanut Butter and Jelly New York Cheesecake Famous Drinks Lemonade Food trivia Cocktail was first made in USA? Created in New Orleans in the mid-1800s, this is one of the first cocktails recognisable by name and remains a favourite to this day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UAE</title>
      <link>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/uae/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 02:30:58 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/uae/</guid>
      <description>Foods you must try Famous foods top 5 Harees Khuzi | The National Dish of UAE Al Machboos, Majboos | The Spicy Chicken! Luqaymat Madrouba Famous Sweets Luqaimat (Lokma (Loukoumades)) Baklava Kunafa: made with spun pastry called kataifi, soaked in a sweet, sugar-based syrup called attar, and typically layered with cheese, or with other ingredients such as clotted cream, pistachio or nuts, depending on the region. Umm Ali Maamoul Chebab Rice Pudding Famous Drinks Arabic coffee KARAK CHAI: is a &amp;ldquo;strong tea&amp;rdquo;, in both taste and colour compared to a regular English tea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>France</title>
      <link>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/france/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 14:06:25 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/france/</guid>
      <description>Foods you must try Famous food top 5 The croissant Escargots: Escargot is the French word for &amp;ldquo;snail,&amp;rdquo; from the Latin conchylium, &amp;ldquo;edible shellfish.&amp;rdquo; Definitions of escargot. edible terrestrial snail usually served in the shell with a sauce of melted butter and garlic. Macarons: A macaron or French macaroon is a sweet meringue-based confection made with egg white, icing sugar, granulated sugar, almond meal, and often food colouring. Jambon-beurre: A jambon-beurre is a French ham sandwich made of a fresh baguette sliced open, spread with butter (salted or unsalted) and filled with slices of ham.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Belgium</title>
      <link>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/belgium/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 10:13:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/belgium/</guid>
      <description>Foods you must try Famous food top 5 Moules frites=Mussels &amp;amp; Fries (Mosselen Met Frietjes, Moules-Frites) Belgian Fries: Belgian fries are just like any other type of deep-fried potato, but one of the secrets is that they are fried twice. Flemish Stew (Stoofvlees, Carbonnades Flamandes): Flemish stew, known in Dutch as stoofvlees or stoverij and in French as carbon(n)ade à la flamande is a Flemish beef (or pork) and onion stew popular in Belgium, the Netherlands and French Flanders, made with beer and mustard spread on bread, seasoning can include bay leaf, thyme, clove and juniper berries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hongkong</title>
      <link>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/hongkong/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 13:09:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/hongkong/</guid>
      <description>Foods/gourmet you must try Famous food top 5 Dimsum: Dim sum is a traditional Chinese meal made up of small plates of dumplings and other snack dishes and is usually accompanied by tea. Dim sum means &amp;rsquo;touch the heart&amp;rsquo; in Chinese. The small portions were designed to merely touch the heart not sate the appetite, and as such were first enjoyed as snacks. 粥 (Congee=Porridge): is a form of rice porridge made by boiling rice in a large amount of water until the rice softens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Malaysia</title>
      <link>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/malaysia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 11:37:53 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/malaysia/</guid>
      <description>Foods/gourmet you must try Famous food top 5 Satay: an Indonesian and Malaysian dish consisting of small pieces of meat grilled on a skewer and served with a spiced sauce that typically contains peanuts. Nasi Lemak: Nasi lemak is a dish originating in Malay cuisine that consists of fragrant rice cooked in coconut milk and pandan leaf. It is commonly found in Malaysia, where it is considered as the national dish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swiss</title>
      <link>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/swiss/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 11:29:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/swiss/</guid>
      <description>Swiss foods/gourmet/gastronomy you must try Famous food top 5 Fondue Fromage/Käsefondue: cheese fondue. Fondue is a Swiss melted cheese and wine dish served in a communal pot over a portable stove heated with a candle or spirit lamp, and eaten by dipping bread into the cheese using long-stemmed forks. Capuns: Capuns is a traditional food from the canton of Graubünden in Switzerland, predominantly made in the eastern part. They are made from Spätzle dough with pieces of dried meat, such as Bündnerfleisch and/or Salsiz, and rolled in a chard leaf.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thailand</title>
      <link>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/thailand/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 09:19:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/thailand/</guid>
      <description>Thailand foods/gourmet you must try Famous food top 5 ต้มยำกุ้ง(Tom yum goong): It&amp;rsquo;s derived from the Thai words “tom,” which refers to the boiling process, “yam,” a Thai spicy and sour salad, and “kung” for shrimp. There&amp;rsquo;s not much information about its origins, but many locals say it&amp;rsquo;s a central Thai soup that emerged due to the abundance of freshwater shrimp mainly from the Chao Phraya River ข้าวมันไก่(Khao Man Gai): Khao Man Gai is often called the Thai variation of Hainanese Chicken Rice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan</title>
      <link>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/taiwan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 11:12:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/taiwan/</guid>
      <description>Taiwan foods/gourmet you must try Famous food top 5 魯肉飯(Lurou fan, Braised pork rice): Khong bah png, as known as Braised pork rice, is a gaifan dish found in Fujianese cuisine and Taiwanese cuisine. Although subject to regional variations, dishes are typically made of pork belly cooked in a process known as lu and served on top of rice. Chinese pickles are often eaten with the dish. 金峰魯肉飯 seems the most famous restaurant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finland</title>
      <link>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/finland/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 12:16:55 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/finland/</guid>
      <description>Finland foods/gourmet you must try Famous food top 5 Lohikeitto: Creamy salmon soup is a common dish in Finland and other Nordic countries. It consists of salmon fillets, boiled potatoes, carrots and leeks. The dish is served hot, and typically seasoned with fresh dill, allspice, salt and black pepper. Poronkäristys(Sautéed reindeer): is perhaps the best known traditional meal from Sápmi in Finland, Sweden, Norway and Russia and Sakha. Usually steak or the back of the reindeer is used.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mallorca</title>
      <link>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/mallorca/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 13:21:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/mallorca/</guid>
      <description>Mallorca foods/gourmet you must try Famous food top 5 Sobrasada: Sobrassada in Balearic or Sobrasada in Spanish, is a raw, cured sausage from the Balearic Islands made with ground pork, paprika, salt and other spices. Pa Amb Oli: Pa amb oli means &amp;ldquo;bread with olive oil&amp;rdquo; in Majorcan, and it is as commonly eaten in the Balearic Islands as pa amb tomàquet is in Catalonia. Frito Mallorquín: Frito Mallorquín is a hearty, nourishing dish that somehow symbolizes the Mallorcan character better than any other food item other than perhaps Sobrassada.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Singapore</title>
      <link>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/singapore/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 11:31:59 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/singapore/</guid>
      <description>Singapore foods/gourmet you must try Famous food top 5 You can&amp;rsquo;t visit Singapore without trying at least some of the items on this list, preferably at a hawker center!
Hainanese Chicken Rice - Tasty chicken with tastier rice. Hainanese chicken rice is a dish of poached chicken and seasoned rice, served with chilli sauce and usually with cucumber garnishes. It was created by immigrants from Hainan in southern China and adapted from the Hainanese dish Wenchang chicken.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Korea</title>
      <link>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/korea/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 10:36:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/korea/</guid>
      <description>South Korea foods/gourmet you must try Famous food top 5 삼겹살(Samgyeopsal): Samgyeopsal, samgyeopsal-gui, or grilled pork belly is a type of gui(grilled dish) in Korean cuisine. 닭갈비(Dak-galbi): Dak-galbi, or spicy stir-fried chicken, is a popular South Korean dish made by stir-frying marinated diced chicken in a gochujang-based sauce with sweet potatoes, cabbage, perilla leaves, scallions, tteok, and other ingredients. In Korean, galbi means rib, and usually refers to braised or grilled short ribs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russia</title>
      <link>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/russia/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 13:44:45 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/russia/</guid>
      <description>Russia foods you must try Famous foods top 5 Сельдь под шубой (Dressed herring): Dressed herring, colloquially known as herring under a fur coat, is a layered salad composed of diced pickled herring covered with layers of grated boiled eggs, vegetables, chopped onions, and mayonnaise. Some variations of this dish include a layer of fresh grated apple while some do not. борщ (Borscht): Borscht is a sour soup, made with meat stock, vegetables and seasonings, common in Eastern Europe and Northern Asia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Italy</title>
      <link>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/italy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 00:11:23 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/italy/</guid>
      <description>Italy foods you must try Famous food top 5 Pasta/Spaghetti Cacio e Pepe: A pasta dish from the cuisine of the city of Rome. Cacio e pepe means &amp;ldquo;cheese and pepper&amp;rdquo; in several central Italian dialects. In keeping with its name, the dish contains grated Pecorino Romano cheese and black pepper, together with spaghetti, or traditionally tonnarelli. Carbonara: Carbonara is a pasta dish made with eggs, hard cheese, cured pork, and black pepper.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
