<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Foods on my trip navigation</title>
    <link>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Foods on my trip navigation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 12:16:55 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://usehttps.github.io/foods/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Finland</title>
      <link>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/finland/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 12:16:55 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/finland/</guid>
      <description>Finland foods/gourmet you must try Famous food top 5 Lohikeitto: Creamy salmon soup is a common dish in Finland and other Nordic countries. It consists of salmon fillets, boiled potatoes, carrots and leeks. The dish is served hot, and typically seasoned with fresh dill, allspice, salt and black pepper. Poronkäristys(Sautéed reindeer): is perhaps the best known traditional meal from Sápmi in Finland, Sweden, Norway and Russia and Sakha. Usually steak or the back of the reindeer is used.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mallorca</title>
      <link>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/mallorca/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 13:21:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/mallorca/</guid>
      <description>Mallorca foods/gourmet you must try Famous food top 5 Sobrasada: Sobrassada in Balearic or Sobrasada in Spanish, is a raw, cured sausage from the Balearic Islands made with ground pork, paprika, salt and other spices. Pa Amb Oli: Pa amb oli means &amp;ldquo;bread with olive oil&amp;rdquo; in Majorcan, and it is as commonly eaten in the Balearic Islands as pa amb tomàquet is in Catalonia. Frito Mallorquín: Frito Mallorquín is a hearty, nourishing dish that somehow symbolizes the Mallorcan character better than any other food item other than perhaps Sobrassada.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Singapore</title>
      <link>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/singapore/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 11:31:59 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/singapore/</guid>
      <description>Singapore foods/gourmet you must try Famous food top 5 You can&amp;rsquo;t visit Singapore without trying at least some of the items on this list, preferably at a hawker center!
Hainanese Chicken Rice - Tasty chicken with tastier rice. Hainanese chicken rice is a dish of poached chicken and seasoned rice, served with chilli sauce and usually with cucumber garnishes. It was created by immigrants from Hainan in southern China and adapted from the Hainanese dish Wenchang chicken.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Korea</title>
      <link>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/korea/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 10:36:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/korea/</guid>
      <description>South Korea foods/gourmet you must try Famous food top 5 삼겹살(Samgyeopsal): Samgyeopsal, samgyeopsal-gui, or grilled pork belly is a type of gui(grilled dish) in Korean cuisine. 닭갈비(Dak-galbi): Dak-galbi, or spicy stir-fried chicken, is a popular South Korean dish made by stir-frying marinated diced chicken in a gochujang-based sauce with sweet potatoes, cabbage, perilla leaves, scallions, tteok, and other ingredients. In Korean, galbi means rib, and usually refers to braised or grilled short ribs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russia</title>
      <link>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/russia/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 13:44:45 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/russia/</guid>
      <description>Russia foods you must try Famous foods top 5 Сельдь под шубой (Dressed herring): Dressed herring, colloquially known as herring under a fur coat, is a layered salad composed of diced pickled herring covered with layers of grated boiled eggs, vegetables, chopped onions, and mayonnaise. Some variations of this dish include a layer of fresh grated apple while some do not. борщ (Borscht): Borscht is a sour soup, made with meat stock, vegetables and seasonings, common in Eastern Europe and Northern Asia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Italy</title>
      <link>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/italy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 00:11:23 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://usehttps.github.io/foods/italy/</guid>
      <description>Italy foods you must try Famous food top 5 Pasta/Spaghetti Cacio e Pepe: A pasta dish from the cuisine of the city of Rome. Cacio e pepe means &amp;ldquo;cheese and pepper&amp;rdquo; in several central Italian dialects. In keeping with its name, the dish contains grated Pecorino Romano cheese and black pepper, together with spaghetti, or traditionally tonnarelli. Carbonara: Carbonara is a pasta dish made with eggs, hard cheese, cured pork, and black pepper.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
